They  drove  the  living  bull  to  the  top  of  the  well  Then  pulled  out  the  well  lid  The  lost  bull  fell  down  in  an  instant  Hear  the  cry  of  the  poor  bull  The  man  came  up  and  shot  Then  he  took  his  son  to  seal  the  well  with  mud  And  they  did  it  Just  to  cover  up  the  wife  who  was  killed  by  him  under  the  well  However,
that  night,
the  bull 's  cry  was  heard  in  the  cow  shed  Will  picked  up  the  hunting  gun  and  came  to  check  But  he  found  that  the  cow  shed  was  full  of  countless  rats  They  all  came  out  of  a  pipe  And  this  pipe  happened  to  go  to  the  well  He  fr antically  looked  inside  Une x pected ly,
the  smell  of  wet  and  smell y  Let  him  vomit  on  the  spot  He  hur ried  up  and  blocked  the  pipe  In  order  to  completely  solve  this  problem  The  next  day,
he  stepped  on  a  bucket  of  water  again  Turn ed  his  head  and  sealed  the  pipe  to  block  the  smell  He  thought  that  all  this  was  done  by  fate  I  don 't  know  if  the  real  trouble  has  just  started  Just  a  month  ago  W ife  inherited  the  land  of  4,
000  ma ids  Plus  his  3,
200  ma ids  Their  family  became  the  most  famous  owner  of  the  local  area  But  in  the  blink  of  an  eye  W ife  wants  to  sell  the  land  Move  to  a  clothing  store  in  the  big  city  He  doesn 't  want  to  stay  in  the  countryside  as  a  farmer  The  couple  also  quar re led  for  this  W ife  even  made  the  worst  plan  That  is  to  sell  the  land  Then  divorce  each  other 's  lives  But  the  son  must  follow  him  to  the  big  city  At  the  same  time,
he  also  told  Will  A  few  days  later,
buyers  will  go  up  and  buy  the  land  This  proposal  was  not  at  all  refused  by  Will  Because  this  is  his  land  He  said  This  word  completely  anger ed  Will  Land  and  son  are  the  most  important  things  in  his  life  And  this  woman  wants  to  take  these  two  things  away  at  the  same  time  This  makes  him  hate  you  gradually  Looking  at  the  axe  in  the  farm  In  his  mind,
a  evil  thought  arises  He  wants  to  kill  his  wife  In  this  way,
he  can  preserve  his  current  life  But  how  to  make  a  perfect  crime  Let  him  take  revenge  After  all,
it  is  almost  impossible  to  hide  his  son  Until  this  day  He  accidentally  met  his  son  and  the  girl  next  door  Stay  together  In  his  mind  Suddenly  flash ed  a  plan  with  no  end  When  he  was  farming  with  his  son  Will  said  sad  A  few  days  later  The  girl  next  door  and  himself  I  can 't  be  by  your  side  anymore  Because  your  mother  wants  to  sell  the  land  Take  you  to  the  city  to  live  Xia owe i  seemed  happy  after  hearing  Just  acquired  the  love  of  life  But  now  tell  him  to  say  goodbye  It 's  unacceptable  to  put  anyone  on  it  Will  took  the  opportunity  to  say  that  he  could  maintain  the  status  quo  But  the  price  is  that  someone  will  be  hurt  in  the  middle  Even  dead  But  this  is  for  15 - year - old  Xia owe i  It 's  something  I  dare  not  think  about  So  he  dared  not  to  make  memories  When  he  ate  at  night  He  begged  his  mother  to  stay  Isn 't  it  good  for  a  family  to  live  a  happy  life  here?  However,